https://www.alaskanorthernlights.com/privacy/

Trustpilot
call us:
PRIVACY
Your security and privacy of information is very important to us!We want your shopping experience to be enjoyable and secure. All credit card and personal information is encrypted, securely transmitted and protected through VeriSign – the leading company in internet security. Any personal information we obtain to complete a sales transaction goes nowhere but into our secure client data files held within our office. No one else has access to this private information and never will. Period.SECURE SHOPPINGWhen you shop at Alaska Northern Lights you will be one of thousands of customers who have already safely shopped with us without credit card fraud.Our goal is that your shopping experience be enjoyable and most of all secure. That is why we guarantee that every transaction you make at Alaska Northern Lights will be 100% safe. Period. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your credit card as a result of shopping at Alaska Northern Lights.To safeguard all your shopping transactions, we employ the latest security methods in protecting your personal information. This includes a Verisign Secure Server Certificate to encrypt your credit card and personal information during a purchase.Our Safe Shopping GuaranteeIf you experience fraudulent use of your credit card as a result of shopping online with Alaska Northern Lights, notify your credit card company in accordance with its rules and procedures. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, Alaska Northern Lights will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00.PRIVACY POLICYYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.The Information We Collect:This notice applies to all information collected or submitted to Alaska Northern Lights’ web site. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:NameAddresses for shipping and billingPhone NumbersEmail addressesCredit or debit card informationThe Way We Use Information:We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data Security:To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.You authorize Alaska Northern Lights to charge you for the order total placed on our website. You further affirm that the name and personal information provided on our forms is true and correct. You further declare that you have read, understand and accept Alaska Northern Lights’s business terms as published on their website. By pressing the Submit Order button, you agree to pay Alaska Northern Lights.How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:We do not maintain any information about you in an online database. All information is secured offline at our offices and cannot be accessed by others. Please call us (See our Contact Page) should you want to know what information we have stored in our files about you. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before providing any information to you.If you have more questions concerning our information policies and your security while shopping from our site, please feel free to contact us.COOKIES POLICYAlaska Northern Lights, Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) uses cookies on the https://www.alaskanorthernlights.com website (the “Service”). By using the Service, you consent to the use of cookies.Our Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, how third-parties we may partner with may use cookies on the Service, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies.What are cookiesCookies are small pieces of text sent to your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Service more useful to you.Cookies can be “persistent” or “session” cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when you go offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser.How Alaska Northern Lights, Inc. uses cookiesWhen you use and access the Service, we may place a number of cookies files in your web browser.We use cookies for the following purposes:To enable certain functions of the ServiceTo provide analyticsWe use both session and persistent cookies on the Service and we use different types of cookies to run the Service:Essential cookies. We may use cookies to remember information that changes the way the Service behaves or looks, such as a user’s language preference on the Service.Analytics cookies. We may use analytics cookies to track information how the Service is used so that we can make improvements. We may also use analytics cookies to test new advertisements, pages, features or new functionality of the Service to see how our users react to them.Third-party cookiesIn addition to our own cookies, we may also use various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the Service, deliver advertisements on and through the Service, and so on.What are your choices regarding cookiesIf you’d like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.For the Chrome web browser, please visit this page from Google: https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050For the Internet Explorer web browser, please visit this page from Microsoft: http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835For the Firefox web browser, please visit this page from Mozilla: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-storedFor the Safari web browser, please visit this page from Apple: https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=en_USFor any other web browser, please visit your web browser’s official web pages.
Online Sale
Free shipping & 25% off!
shop now
Trustpilot
Our Clients
I am so glad I discovered the lightbox and strongly recommend it to anyone who suffers from Seasonal Affective Disorder!
Heidi GWest Grove, PA
Several months ago, I was seeing a sleep therapist for fatigue and "unrestful" sleep. She suggested I try a light box. I am very happy with my purchase.
T.S.Minneapolis, MN
This is our family's third winter using our lightbox. We are extremely happy we decided to purchase this lightbox!
The Ricker FamilyJuneau, AK
For such a small light, it emits a lot of light, which makes it easier in the morning. I would definitely recommend buying one!
Brooke CDuluth, MN
As an added bonus the light box is a fabulous make-up light. Since moving my light box and using it every day, I feel great!
Kathy RKingston, MA
I have had great benefit from daily use of my light box. Just having it on for 20 to 30 minutes a day has helped improve my mood and energy.
Michael S. Langan, MD FACPColumbus, OH
Since getting my light box, the harsh winters here haven't seemed so dreary, and my mood hasn't had the usual winter 'dip' I used to have.
Ben MLakewood, OH
I was surprised at how easy it was to use the Aurora LightPad MAX. It's small and compact, making it easy for me to use anywhere in my house.
Ryan M.Seattle, WA
My doctor suggested I purchased a SAD light box and I'm so happy to have found the Aurora Lightpad mini. I use it every day and call it my happy light.
Audry BellPittsburgh, PA
I bought the lightpad to help with my winter blues. We had a long and dark winter and I was ready to try anything to make a positive impact.
Kevin R.Hudson, WI
Previous
Next
PRODUCTS
Insurance Form
Lightbox Uses
Shipping & Handling
User Guides
Warranty Registration
Alaska Northern Lights, Inc.59 Damonte Ranch Pkwy #B-262Reno, NV 89521P: 1-800-880-6953F: (775) 622-8060info@alaskanorthernlights.comM-F 8:00am – 5:00pm PST
